Roy Justus Papers
Roy Justus Papers
- Artwork
  - By Justus
    - 1952 Jul-Dec, 131 items (Oversize 11)
      Jul 28: Thank you - we'll take the nonsense
      Jul 30: As if he hasn't enough to worry about already!
      Jul 31: Threatened slave shortage
      Aug 1: Grimier and grimier
      Aug 2: You can lead a donkey to water, but-
      Aug 4: The lull before the storm
      Aug 5: Fat boy of the Arab world
      Aug 6: This music hath charm
      Aug 7: Striking a mighty blow for liberty
      Aug 8: Hitch-hiker
      Aug 9: And no letters, please!
      Aug 11: Time's a-wastin!
      Aug 12: Family dog
      Aug 13: Not this time
      Aug 14: Good trick if he can do it
      Aug 15: And won't be in November
      Aug 16: Bear market
      Aug 18: The whip hand
      Sep 6: Now for a straight furrow!
      Sep 9: ...and he'd always said: there ain't no such animal
      Sep 10: One vote lost
      Sep 11: Me-ow-w-w!
      Sep 12: She ain't mad at nobody
      Sep 13: Didn't even leave a scar!
      Sep 15: The 64-dollar question
      Sep 16: Return visit
      Sep 17: That man is here again
      Sep 18: Depends upon the view point
      Sep 19: Walls of Jericho
      Sep 20: Looking at the records
      Sep 22: Will he muff this one?
      Sep 23: Nixon!
      Sep 25: Spotlighting it
      Sep 26: Cooking on the front burner
      Sep 29: Oops, sorry!
      Sep 30: Anybody else want to run?
      Oct 1: Longest swan song in history
      Oct 2: To some ears it's monotonous
      Oct 3: President of the U.S.A. debates the issues
      Oct 4: And 364 other days, too!
      Oct 6: Book of the month
      Oct 7: 27 more days to save your country
      Oct 8: Eclipse?
      Oct 9: Is this the main tent or a side show?
      Oct 10: Flight's end
      Oct 11: Race with the stork
      Oct 13: Adlai's lamb has quit following
      Oct 14: Most popular fellow in the nation
      Oct 15: Don't let them take it away-???
      Oct 16: Urgent unpartisan business
      Oct 17: It's in the bag!
      Oct 18: Running interference
      Oct 20: Experience says: keeping on chopping wood
      Oct 21: Can he carry him 'til Nov. 4?
      Oct 22: No cause for alarm
      Oct 23: Melancholy days
      Oct 24: I fa' down!
      Oct 25: When will Adlai get around to this?
      Oct 27: The goblins again
      Oct 29: Is this the clean up in Washington?
      Oct 31: What this country needs-
      Nov 1: And time is running out!
      Nov 3: Well?
      Nov 4: Judgment day
      Nov 5: Two minds with a single thought
      Nov 6: Phew!
      Nov 7: What a nice job that would be!
      Nov 10: Unscrambling the omelet
      Nov 11: All right, all right - you drive
      Nov 12: Signs of the times?
      Nov 13: Feeling better already?
      Nov 14: He's just not used to that sort of thing
      Nov 15: The conference
      Nov 17: Shifting the burdens has its problems, too
      Nov 18: The shock was terrifying
      Nov 19: For him, there isn't
      Nov 20: The interregnum
      Nov 21: Director of the budget
      Nov 22: Hostile Indians are showing up
      Nov 24: Invigorating
      Nov 25: Tough bargainer
      Nov 26: The toast
      Nov 27: Still much to be thankful for
      Nov 28: Yakity-yak
      Nov 29: This is the time of change
      Dec 1: Harmony
      Dec 2: Last gravy train now leaving
      Dec 3: Russian peace ballet
      Dec 4: Another political argument settled
      Dec 5: Try it on just for size
      Dec 6: There's one in every crowd
      Dec 8: This is the charitable season
      Dec 9: Match maker
      Dec 10: Season's greetings
      Dec 11: Somebody's ears are burning
      Dec 12: The great balancing act
      Dec 13: Double purpose nut cracker
      Dec 15: Long wait for that inaugural special
      Dec 16: Christmas in Moscow
      Dec 17: Casualty
      Dec 18: The Christmas wreath for many
      Dec 19: Harassed nursemaid
      Dec 20: Mind if I have a look?
      Dec 22: The cynic
      Dec 23: Better too late than never
      Dec 24: By golly - I believe this is the summit!
      Dec 25: A message to Garcia
      Dec 26: My gosh - here comes another one!
      Dec 27: Open with caution
      Dec 29: The inquiring reporters
      Dec 30: The grand finale
    - 1953 Jan-Jun, 149 items (Oversize 12)
      Jan 1: Here, kid - you find the answers!
      Jan 2: Doesn't know where to begin
      Jan 8: The victor and the vanquished
      Jan 9: Birth of a new administration
      Jan 10: Which ax
      Jan 12: January thaw
      Jan 13: Looking the gift horse in the mouth
      Jan 14: Luxuries are returning to western Europe
      Jan 15: Another page from the master
      Jan 16: And last - the z-bomb
      Jan 17: Mustn't touch!
      Jan 19: Harry has left some booby traps
      Jan 20: After 20 years in the wilderness
      Jan 21: Quite a chance at the office!
      Jan 22: Now, let's see - which comes first
      Jan 23: Ike ain't only wun wid troubles!
      Jan 24: He'll have his own little garden
      Jan 26: Knotty problems
      Jan 27: The c-c-cold war
      Jan 28: From whipping boy to public servant
      Jan 29: Brothers under the skin
      Jan 30: Trade not aid
      Jan 31: Ghost writer
      Feb 2: Chief's special
      Feb 3: Spinach. Before the cake
      Feb 4: Chickens home to roost
      Feb 5: Bronco buster
      Feb 6: Getting the works
      Feb 7: No timid soul, he!
      Feb 9: Howdy neighbour!
      Feb 10: Look who's back in town
      Feb 11: How'd that get in the act?
      Feb 12: Hope springs eternal
      Feb 13: How much will the traffic bear?
      Feb 14: Man at work
      Feb 17: Wasting ammunition - and dangerous, too!
      Feb 18: I'm just looking
      Feb 19: The farmer in the dell
      Feb 20: The briar pipe case
      Feb 21: Thought, I was neglectin' you, huh?
      Feb 23: First test of strength
      Feb 24: U.N. delegate and pet arrive
      Feb 25: More complicated than I thought!
      Feb 26: Retreat from Moscow
      Feb 27: The old meanie!
      Feb 28: Horns of the dilemma
      Mar 2: The month of spring is here
      Mar 3: The replacement has arrived
      Mar 4: Psychological warfare
      Mar 5: Stalin's rule has ended
      Mar 6: About this time of year
      Mar 7: Watchful waiting
      Mar 8: New weather flag has gone up
      Mar 9: New face on the drawing board
      Mar 10: The roll of the dice
      Mar 11: And then the American home?
      Mar 12: Isn't that Joe's old bird?
      Mar 13: Enslaved
      Mar 14: Paternity case
      Mar 16: Will it come to this?
      Mar 17: War of nerves and the new boss
      Mar 18: May this test never be made!
      Mar 19: Fishin' can't be that good!
      Mar 20: Down to fundamentals
      Mar 21: Are you listening?
      Mar 23: Excuse us if we seem suspicious
      Mar 24: He sees something already
      Mar 25: Two-party senator
      Mar 26: The nerve!
      Mar 27: No ammunition shortage here!
      Mar 28: A needed investigation
      Mar 30: Good news - may be!
      Mar 31: Is it the same old recipe book?
      Apr 1: Finding a good security risk isn't easy!
      Apr 2: Completing the inauguration
      Apr 3: Is he selling something?
      Apr 4: Cut it out - we've got work to do!
      Apr 6: Goldilocks will have to be on guard
      Apr 7: The confession
      Apr 8: The falconer
      Apr 9: April showers
      Apr 10: Picture of a very busy man
      Apr 11: Jack-in-a-box
      Apr 13: Longest incubation in history
      Apr 14: Too much noise from the gallery
      Apr 15: He only offered to hold it a while!
      Apr 16: A matter of balance
      Apr 17: Grooving one for him
      Apr 18: Has spring come for him
      Apr 20: Whittling away
      Apr 21: When will they free this prisoner?
      Apr 22: Anybody got a life preserver?
      Apr 23: After 35 years of covered clocks
      Apr 24: 0 for the touch of a vanished hand-
      Apr 25: Wow-w-w!
      Apr 26: Get thee behind me!
      Apr 27: The mountain must come to Mahomet
      Apr 28: Why should I have to register?
      Apr 29: So far, so good
      Apr 30: Ike's on the offensive
      May 1: He's certainly doing something!
      May 2: Washington style note
      May 4: Little red riding hood
      May 5: A little brain washing of his own
      May 6: Strange how quiet the bedfellows!
      May 7: The left hand and the right hand
      May 9: Will-o'-the-wisp?
      May 11: He's almost made up his mind
      May 12: I just can't read the bottom lines, doc!
      May 13: Bringing an emblem up to date
      May 14: A torch without light
      May 15: So far his most lethal weapon
      May 16: The pig in a poke
      May 18: Running away from home isn't
      May 19: Even an elephant is not heavy enough
      May 20: Woodman, spare that tree!
      May 21: The price of liberty
      May 22: H-m-m-m!
      May 23: The hand is quicker than the eye
      May 25: There is a new spring in his walk
      May 26: Before its gets beyond repair
      May 27: Suspense
      May 28: Sour note at the rehearsal
      May 29: Co-chairman, joint chiefs of staff
      May 30: Peace has come to many
      Jun 1: Nothing would please him more
      Jun 2: Making it easy for the president
      Jun 3: Still other Everests
      Jun 4: The large economy package
      Jun 4: Diplomas are becoming more burdensome
      Jun 5: Fog
      Jun 8: These things make a lot of noise
      Jun 9: Mary's lamb
      Jun 10: The people are still with him
      Jun 11: Uncle will have to watch this
      Jun 12: Party of the opposition
      Jun 15: Drill sergeant
      Jun 16: Now what do you suppose he means?
      Jun 17: Babe in the tariff woods
      Jun 18: Wish we could throw the big one back
      Jun 19: Can he take it?
      Jun 20: We need a dual purpose ice pack
      Jun 22: Among those set free
      Jun 23: The mirage
      Jun 24: If we could only have a look!
      Jun 25: Snafu
      Jun 26: The thundering herd
      Jun 29: Temporary haven for Georgi
      Jun 30: New sign for our foreign friends
    - 1953 Jul-Dec, 129 items (Oversize 13)
      Jul 1: Washington DC
      Jul 2: Dat ol' debbil again!
      Jul 3: Accenting it
      Jul 4: Freedom celebration
      Jul 6: Ever hear the story about the fighting rabbit?
      Jul 7: Teamwork
      Jul 9: The good ship one world
      Jul 10: It'll take a lot of brain washing
      Jul 13: Until only one is left
      Jul 14: The race is on
      Jul 15: Bumper crops
      Jul 16: Busy life guard
      Jul 17: The bear's dilemma
      Jul 18: Undisputed world champ
      Jul 20: The inquisitor
      Jul 21: Quite an arsenal
      Jul 22: Traffic signal
      Jul 23: Early applicant
      Jul 24: One man's meat is another man's poison
      Jul 25: And 275,000,000,000 pounds of pressure
      Jul 27: Unfinished business
      Jul 28: The first time in history
      Jul 29: Back to the farm movement
      Jul 30: Humpty dumpty
      Aug 4: Guns and butter
      Aug 5: Now to demonstrate
      Aug 6: Appraising Ike's first six months
      Aug 7: Not exactly picnic weather
      Aug 8: The man to turn to
      Aug 10: International zoo
      Aug 11: Another case of atomic secrecy
      Aug 12: Mr. Big
      Aug 13: Misery loves company
      Aug 14: Wrong club, john!
      Aug 15: The agenda
      Aug 17: Weather vane: wow!
      Aug 18: Big but not bottomless
      Aug 19: Sort of window shopping
      Aug 20: More money
      Aug 21: It is for hell bomb
      Aug 22: I've got one, too!
      Aug 24: On the hustings
      Sep 15: Party psychiatrist
      Sep 16: Counter crusade
      Sep 17: The way of the aggressor is hard
      Sep 18: We keep trying
      Sep 19: If it isn't one surplus it's another
      Sep 21: Same old road
      Sep 22: All right, where is the rabbit?
      Sep 26: Swish!
      Sep 28: Georgi!
      Sep 29: Concerning the highway killer
      Sep 30: Gentlemen, be seated!
      Oct 1: Greatest issue of the day
      Oct 2: Two fellows with something in common
      Oct 3: Expediency makes strange bedfellows
      Oct 5: Adult education
      Oct 6: Balancing act
      Oct 7: Sounds like a war cry
      Oct 8: Another repatriation problem
      Oct 9: Lowest form of human life
      Oct 10: This hunting season is always open
      Oct 11: Atomic question
      Oct 12: Always standard equipment on this car
      Oct 13: Kids will be kids
      Oct 14: The anchor men
      Oct 16: Experience is great teacher
      Oct 17: Test of skill
      Oct 19: Might as well go ahead and show him
      Oct 20: Sooner or later he'll have to stand on his own feet
      Oct 21: All dressed up for '54
      Oct 23: Halloween in Europe
      Oct 24: The toll goes up and up
      Oct 26: Phantom or reality?
      Oct 27: Inflation is still with us
      Oct 27: Somebody has lost something
      Oct 28: A couple of very busy farmers
      Oct 29: Comforting thought for the day
      Oct 30: B-but, it really is a wolf!
      Oct 31: The lady at Panmunjom
      Nov 2: Not as sweet as used to be!
      Nov 4: Disillusioned neutral
      Nov 5: There's another one!
      Nov 6: Graphic art
      Nov 7: Perilous security
      Nov 9: Tomorrow is safer Minneapolis day
      Nov 10: Anyway it won't be dull
      Nov 11: The open door
      Nov 12: Boy - oh boy - oh boy!
      Nov 13: Right in the middle
      Nov 14: The millennium has not arrived
      Nov 16: Boys! Boys!
      Nov 17: Korean famine
      Nov 18: Bi-partisan policy
      Nov 19: The guide
      Nov 20: What a time for flying-saucer stories
      Nov 21: Injuns!
      Nov 23: Isn't it time to change records?
      Nov 24: Korean pipe of peace
      Nov 25: King Canute sweeps back the waves
      Nov 26: Yes - we should be thankful
      Nov 27: Un-American activities
      Nov 28: Not the walls of Jericho, Georgi!
      Nov 30: Little red riding hood
      Dec 1: Just in the nick of the time again
      Dec 2: It just had to come to this!
      Dec 3: Bermuda exercises
      Dec 4: The patience of Job
      Dec 5: Now to find a place to hang it
      Dec 7: Hard to distinguish one from the other
      Dec 8: Ike has the ball
      Dec 9: More than a one-man job!
      Dec 10: And avoid the rush
      Dec 11: Can you beat it?
      Dec 12: And still another atom blast
      Dec 15: Hot stuff
      Dec 16: The rehearsal
      Dec 17: Harsh Yule tide note
      Dec 18: The cynic
      Dec 19: Dear Santa
      Dec 21: Christmas card
      Dec 22: Competition
      Dec 23: Hopeful, but cautious
      Dec 24: The fortune tellers
      Dec 25: Merry Christmas
      Dec 26: Party of the opposition - Russian style
      Dec 28: And keep it!
      Dec 29: Time marches on
      Dec 30: No hard feelings of course
    - 1954 Jan-Jun, 150 items (Oversize 14)
      Jan 1: All the world's a stage
      Jan 2: Speaking softly !
      Jan 4: Fireworks for 1954!
      Jan 5: Ike reports to the nation
      Jan 6: And, of course, lots of pepper!
      Jan 7: State of the union
      Jan 8: The duet
      Jan 9: How to find the needle in the haystack
      Jan 10: Two points of view
      Jan 11: The talk stage
      Jan 12: Into the hopper
      Jan 13: Having his fun spoiled for him
      Jan 14: Milking time
      Jan 15: Came the revolution
      Jan 18: Not too well concealed
      Jan 19: Just a nuisance around here anyway
      Jan 20: Going high hat on us?
      Jan 21: May not miss the boat after all?
      Jan 22: More hot potatoes
      Jan 23: Parity!
      Jan 25: The conference
      Jan 27: Who would put uncle in the stocks?
      Jan 28: Same stuffed dove?
      Jan 29: Super patriot
      Jan 30: His soft spot
      Feb 1: How to get the eagle back in the shell?
      Feb 2: The days are getting longer
      Feb 3: Viewing it dimly
      Feb 4: When is an economist not an economist?
      Feb 5: Developing immunity
      Feb 6: Shucks, that depression is already here!
      Feb 8: The heckler
      Feb 9: Emergency fence mender
      Feb 10: Clarifying the issues
      Feb 11: Now where else does it hurt?
      Feb 12: Global significance
      Feb 13: Russia's big four conference terms
      Feb 15: The chance of a life time!
      Feb 16: Same old look
      Feb 17: Getting rid of the surplus
      Feb 18: Decoration
      Feb 19: Just in case he grows into a tiger!
      Feb 20: Just to avoid misunderstanding
      Feb 22: The Washington cherry tree
      Feb 23: Doubled-edged ax
      Feb 24: His very existence depends on it
      Feb 25: This is not brotherhood street
      Feb 26: Bear by the tail?
      Feb 27: Melon stealin' time
      Mar 1: Far cry from the cold war
      Mar 2: Another propaganda opportunity
      Mar 4: Tax headaches
      Mar 5: Which is the elephant boy?
      Mar 6: Lot of meat for a former vegetarian
      Mar 8: The salesman
      Mar 9: The unheeded traffic sign
      Mar 10: Bedtime stories
      Mar 11: The mountain labored
      Mar 12: An old political custom
      Mar 13: The threat from within
      Mar 16: Ouch!
      Mar 17: Nothing like a lot of spice
      Mar 18: Now chasing his own tail
      Mar 19: Poof! - there goes another island
      Mar 20: The new look
      Mar 22: Piggy-back
      Mar 23: Boy at the dike
      Mar 24: Baby-a-bomb
      Mar 25: The surplus problems
      Mar 26: Old carnival act
      Mar 27: Complete defense against the h-bomb
      Mar 29: Up in a cloud
      Mar 30: Early arrivals
      Mar 31: It's a long, hard winter
      Apr 1: Manna!
      Apr 2: Her protector
      Apr 3: Into the woods
      Apr 5: New commanding officer
      Apr 6: Still doesn't resemble a dove
      Apr 7: European gardening
      Apr 8: Priority
      Apr 9: Waiting for the guest of honor
      Apr 10: Something new for uncle
      Apr 12: Speaking of trade barriers
      Apr 13: Reluctant fireman
      Apr 14: Spring tonic
      Apr 15: Packing for the Geneva conference
      Apr 16: Wait- it can't be that bad!
      Apr 17: Some people just don't like to fly
      Apr 19: Too much even for him?
      Apr 20: Ringside seat
      Apr 21: Going somewhere
      Apr 22: Fear is nothing new
      Apr 23: Cross fire
      Apr 24: A woman's work is never done
      Apr 26: Race with the stroke
      Apr 27: Broken record
      Apr 28: Elusive butterfly
      Apr 29: Doesn't he deserve a medal or something?
      Apr 30: The two are in complete agreement
      May 1: This picture is quite clear
      May 3: Fish requires patience
      May 5: Difficult enough without a handicap
      May 6: Happy days
      May 7: Night works
      May 8: Well, if it is not Cap'n Rip van Winkle!
      May 10: China's open door
      May 11: Their ears to the ground
      May 12: It's been kinda dry
      May 13: Ladi-e-e-es an' gentlemen!
      May 14: Three is a crowd
      May 15: Conservation for wild life, too!
      May 17: Sh-h-h-h!
      May 18: New era in the far east
      May 19: The condemned
      May 20: Notice to trespassers
      May 21: Book salesman
      May 22: Gideon d. Seymour
      May 24: Volunteer fireman
      May 25: The brickbats go with the job
      May 26: He smells honey
      May 27: Problem child
      May 28: Ominous cloud over Washington
      May 29: Requiescat in pace
      Jun 1: Much needed investigation
      Jun 2: Final exams!
      Jun 3: The whole kit and caboodle
      Jun 4: The Geneva conference
      Jun 5: Will it be a good or evil genie?
      Jun 7: Fate of the brave seafaring man
      Jun 8: Monitoring can be such fun
      Jun 9: Out of the chute
      Jun 10: Mein Kampf - American version
      Jun 11: Sitting on it
      Jun 12: He can't have one without the other
      Jun 14: And without senatorial immunity!
      Jun 15: Between the devil and the deep sea, blue sea
      Jun 16: From Panmunjom to Geneva
      Jun 17: Political courtesy
      Jun 18: The custodian
      Jun 19: Who said he's finished?
      Jun 20: When Sunday painters
      Jun 21: This is not bear country
      Jun 22: Memo from Washington
      Jun 23: As Maine goes, so goes nation
      Jun 24: War was never like this!
      Jun 26: Away from it all
      Jun 28: Will this be the big one that got away?
      Jun 29: Will this satisfy his hunger
      Jun 30: Above, and beyond the call of duty?
    - 1954 Jul-Dec, 137 items (Oversize 15)
      Jul 1: Busy days for the rival suitors
      Jul 2: And almost as short!
      Jul 3: From both home and abroad
      Jul 5: Good or bad medicine?
      Jul 6: Boy with a bent pin
      Jul 7: Man watching atomic arms race
      Jul 8: Bear trap
      Jul 9: Clean hands might help
      Jul 10: Dispossessed
      Jul 12: Remarkable recuperative powers
      Jul 13: No customers
      Jul 15: Budgetary problems
      Jul 16: Move over!
      Jul 17: Speaker's platform isn't quite ready
      Jul 18: Torch bearer
      Jul 19: Folks don't stop as much now-a-days!
      Jul 20: Chief problem of coexistence
      Jul 21: Travelling man
      Jul 22: The one that didn't get away
      Jul 23: Bound to blow up a storm
      Jul 24: The needle in the haystack
      Jul 25: Heck- why wait till vacation time?
      Jul 27: How long a flight
      Jul 28: Now it's her turn
      Jul 29: Joe doesn't answer questions
      Jul 30: Of course, the itinerary can be changed
      Jul 31: The smoke won't clear til November
      Aug 1: Wonder why?
      Aug 2: Now on the last chapter
      Aug 3: Out of hearing range
      Aug 4: Greetings
      Aug 5: Injuns!
      Aug 6: Left holding the can
      Aug 7: Cramped quarters
      Aug 9: Already pointing with pride!
      Aug 10: Changing the slogan
      Aug 11: Farming's no snap!
      Aug 12: Hitch-hiker's advice
      Aug 13: The draft is getting stronger
      Aug 14: The anti-communism series
      Aug 16: The meeting of east and west
      Aug 17: Political hash! Political hash!
      Aug 18: Honorable intentions?
      Aug 19: Every two years
      Aug 20: Power - steering
      Aug 21: Superman
      Aug 23: Developing a taste for it?
      Sep 14: Sowing where the soil is fertile
      Sep 15: Picking up the pieces
      Sep 16: Double handicap
      Sep 17: His secret weapon?
      Sep 18: Buttons will be larger this year!
      Sep 20: He's got 'em guessing again!
      Sep 21: Will this become a marathon?
      Sep 22: Looking for a place to test it
      Sep 23: Aw - come on out!
      Sep 24: These are nerve racking days!
      Sep 25: Stirred up something!
      Sep 27: Now do-it-yourself devotee
      Sep 28: The ticketless rider
      Sep 29: Double pressure
      Sep 30: Tough spot for William Tell
      Oct 1: Learning to live with him isn't easy
      Oct 2: And 364 other days!
      Oct 4: Optimistic gravediggers
      Oct 5: Over confidence is no problem
      Oct 6: The big beneficiary
      Oct 7: Adult delinquency
      Oct 8: Is this your handwriting?
      Oct 9: Bouncing crystal ball
      Oct 11: Isn't this interference or something?
      Oct 13: Tweet
      Oct 14: Fine place for a bird dog!
      Oct 15: Good little boys and temptation
      Oct 16: Burying the hatchet
      Oct 18: New seating arrangement
      Oct 19: 99.3% pure
      Oct 20: Trick or treats!
      Oct 21: Precarious romance
      Oct 22: The package
      Oct 22: Lateral to the coach
      Oct 25: Somehow that claw looks familiar
      Oct 26: Speaking of bird dogs
      Oct 27: Now up to the man with the pencil
      Oct 28: Little red riding hood up-to-date
      Oct 30: Vantage point
      Nov 2: German unification - Moscow style
      Nov 3: No rest for the weary
      Nov 4: The 64 dollar question
      Nov 5: Election statistic
      Nov 6: No cause for grieve
      Nov 8: The times demand it
      Nov 9: Sailor, beware!
      Nov 10: Thus endeth the 83rd congress
      Nov 11: Veterans day 1954
      Nov 12: Thorny question
      Nov 12: All dressed up and no place to go